<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ex4</string>
    <string name="movie_title_1">Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace</string>
    <string name="movie_title_2">Star Wars Episode II: Attack of the Clones</string>
    <string name="movie_title_3">Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith</string>
    <string name="movie_title_4">Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope</string>
    <string name="movie_title_5">Star Wars Episode V: Empire Strikes Back</string>
    <string name="movie_title_6">Star Wars Episode VI: Return of the Jedi</string>
    <string name="movie_title_7">Star Wars Episode VII: The Force Awakens</string>
    <string name="movie_title_8">Star Wars Episode VIII: The Last Jedi</string>
    <string name="movie_title_9">Rogue One: A Star Wars Story</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_1">
        The first movie chronologically, this movie tells the story of how Obi-Wan Kenobi
        first found Anakin Skywalker, the "Chosen One", and the events that lead to him joining
        the Jedi Order. </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_2">
        Set ten years after the first movie, this tells the story of how Anakin grows into his role
        in the Order, and is also the beginning of the Clone Wars (a rather good animated adaptation
        of the Clone Wars exists).</string>
    <string name="movie_desc_3">
        This is the movie that rounds out the prequels, and it tells the story of Anakin\'s fall
        to the Dark Side. Manipulated by Darth Sidious, he turns on his old master and the Jedi Order
        in order to save his wife from dying. This culminates with him becoming Darth Vader.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_4">
        The first of the Star Wars movies to be released, it tells the story of Luke Skywalker.
        He joins the Rebellion and meets Princess Leia, old man Obi-Wan, ruggedly handsome rogue
        Han Solo and his companion Chewbacca.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_5">
        Luke\'s story continues in this movie, where he learns more of the ways of the Force from
        Master Yoda. He also faces off with Darth Vader, and learns something very important about
        his origins.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_6">
        Luke tries to retrieve his comrade Han Solo from the clutches of Jabba the Hutt, and also
        leads a war against the Empire. He faces off with the man who turned his father to the
        Dark Side, and finally frees the Galaxy from the clutches of the Sith.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_7">
        The new trilogy introduces us to Rey, Finn, Poe Dameron and Kylo Ren. Kylo Ren is Darth Vader\'s
        grandson and desperately trying to live up to his name. A new threat has taken over the
        galaxy in the ashes of the Empire.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_8">
        Rey has found Luke Skywalker, and is attempting to learn from him. However, Luke is reluctant,
        and feels the galaxy would be better off without the Jedi. Kylo Ren and Rey deepen their
        relationship, and there are major shifts in the power balance.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_desc_9">
        Taking place between Episode III and Episode IV, this movie tells the tale of Jyn Erso,
        the daughter of the creator of the Death Star. She helps the rebels acquire the plans,
        and tries to get her father back from the Empire that kidnapped him.
    </string>
    <string name="movie_covers">Movie covers</string>
    <string name="choose_movie">Choose movie:</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <string-array name="movie_titles">
        <item>@string/movie_title_1</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_2</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_3</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_4</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_5</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_6</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_7</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_8</item>
        <item>@string/movie_title_9</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_descriptions">
        <item>@string/movie_desc_1</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_2</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_3</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_4</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_5</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_6</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_7</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_8</item>
        <item>@string/movie_desc_9</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="movie_covers">
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_7</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_8</item>
        <item>@drawable/star_wars_9</item>
    </array>
</resources>
